

CONTACT

- **4** +49 15255 764358
- anjakhan@gmx.de
- Strausberg (near Berlin)
- anjakhan.netlify.app
- github.com/anjakhan

EDUCATION

GIS-Analyst GIS-Akademie Berlin Jan 2016 - Aug 2016

M. Sc. Environmental Science Ernst-Moritz-Arndt Universität Greifswald 2013 - 2015

SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

React/Redux

Node.js

Leaflet

Git & GitHub

Babel & Webpack

Bootstrap

GatsbyJS & GraphQL

PostgreSQL / MS SQL Server

ArcGIS / QGIS

Pvthon

LANGUAGES

German - Native Speaker

Russian - A2 Level

English - Fluent

ANJA KHAN

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Solution-driven Fullstack Web Developer, whose passion develops more with every day of self-study in programming. The foundation for coding was set in a GIS-Analyst course. Alongside my first jobs I became a self taught Fullstack Developer knowing HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript well. Besides I have a good understanding of React/Redux and Node.js. Real life experience I achieved in working with Python, SQL (PostgreSQL, MS SQL), the above mentioned frontend languages as well as Leaflet. I am currently deep diving into the modern advanced JavaScript practices. Looking for a new challenge, where I can bring in my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IBE - Ingenieurbüro Dr. Eckhof GmbH / GIS-Analyst/IT-Specialist

January 2018 - present, Ahrensfelde

Responsible and independent processing of projects and tasks in all areas and fields of activity of the IBE engineering office Dr. Eckhof GmbH (immission forecast, landscape planning) as well as IT specialist for ArcGIS, database and server administration.

ÖKO-DATA GmbH (now IBE GmbH) / GIS-Analyst/IT-Specialist

May 2017 - December 2017, Strausberg

Responsible and independent processing of projects and tasks in all areas and fields of activity of the ÖKO-DATA GmbH (critical loads, landscape planning) as well as IT specialist for ArcGIS, database and server administration.

WISA-Laboratorium GmbH / Scientific Worker

January 2017 - May 2017, Schwedt

Implementation of quality assurance measures as department head of the water laboratory and execution of chemical analyzes.

CERTIFICATES

Complete React Developer in 2021 (w/ Redux, Hooks, GraphQL)

November 2020, Udemy

Credential URL: udemy.com/certificate/UC-90f3126e-8e0c-4c18-a9a1-74f83ef41ef7

The Complete Web Developer in 2020: Zero to Mastery

May 2020, Udemy

Credential URL: udemy.com/certificate/UC-7b82da75-6cbe-46c4-a18d-e3a5412df004

Display and analyze GIS data on the web with Leaflet

November 2018, Udemy

Credential URL: udemy.com/certificate/UC-GNFK8N4V



ANJA (RITTER) KHAN

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

KONTAKT

- **4** +49 15255 764358
- anjakhan@gmx.de
- Strausberg (bei Berlin)
- ☐ anjakhan.netlify.app
- github.com/anjakhan

AUSBILDUNG

GIS-Analyst

GIS-Akademie Berlin Jan 2016 - Aug 2016

M. Sc. Umweltwissenschaften

Ernst-Moritz-Arndt Universität

Greifswald

2013 - 2015

FÄHIGKEITEN

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

React/Redux

Node.is

Leaflet

Git & GitHub

Babel & Webpack

Bootstrap

GatsbyJS & GraphQL

PostgreSQL / MS SQL Server

ArcGIS / QGIS

Python

SPRACHEN

Deutsch - Muttersprache

Englisch - C1 Level

Russisch - A2 Level

PROFIL

Lösungs-orientierte Web Entwicklerin, deren Leidenschaft für die Programmierung im Selbststudium täglich wächst. Die Grundlage für das Programmieren wurde in einem GIS-Analyst-Kurs gelegt. Neben meinen ersten Jobs entwickelte ich mich zu einer autodidaktischen Fullstack Web Entwicklerin, die HTML5, CSS3 und JavaScript gut beherrscht. Außerdem habe ich ein gutes Verständnis von React/Redux und Node.js. Praxiserfahrungen sammelte ich in der Arbeit mit Python, SQL (PostgreSQL, MS SQL), den oben genannten Frontend-Sprachen sowie Leaflet. Derzeit suche ich nach einer neuen Herausforderung, in der ich meine IT-Skills sinnvoll anwenden und erweitern kann.

BERUFSERFAHRUNG

IBE - Ingenieurbüro Dr. Eckhof GmbH / GIS-Analyst/IT-Spezialist

Januar 2018 - heute, Ahrensfelde

Eigenverantwortliche und selbstständige Bearbeitung von Projekten und Aufgaben auf allen Gebieten und Tätigkeitsfeldern der IBE-Ingenieurbüro Dr. Eckhof GmbH (Immissionsprognostik, Landschaftsplanung) sowie IT-Spezialistin für ArcGIS-, Datenbank- und Serveradministration.

ÖKO-DATA GmbH (jetzt IBE GmbH) / GIS-Analyst/IT-Spezialist

Mai 2017 - Dezember 2017, Strausberg

Eigenverantwortliche und selbstständige Bearbeitung von Projekten und Aufgaben auf allen Gebieten und Tätigkeitsfeldern der ÖKO-DATA GmbH (Critical Loads, Landschaftsplanung) sowie IT-Spezialistin für ArcGIS-, Datenbank- und Serveradministration.

WISA-Laboratorium GmbH / Wissenschaftliche Mitarbeiterin

Januar 2017 - Mai 2017. Schwedt

Durchführung qualitätssichernder Maßnahmen als Fachbereichsleiterin des Wasserlabors sowie Ausführung chemischer Analysen.

ZERTIFIKATE

Complete React Developer in 2021 (w/ Redux, Hooks, GraphQL)

November 2020, Udemy

Credential URL: udemy.com/certificate/UC-90f3126e-8e0c-4c18-a9a1-74f83ef41ef7

The Complete Web Developer in 2020: Zero to Mastery

Mai 2020, Udemy

Credential URL: udemy.com/certificate/UC-7b82da75-6cbe-46c4-a18d-e3a5412df004

Display and analyze GIS data on the web with Leaflet

November 2018, Udemy

Credential URL: udemy.com/certificate/UC-GNFK8N4V